Saratoga Springs Open Space Project; Records apap155
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programs and Issues, 1970-1972; 1981-1986; 1989-2002; 3; 4.36 cubic ft.
  - "Saratoga County chamber again looking for home"Daily Gazette, 1996 November 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 155)
  - "Ballston Spa to get up to 200 new jobs"Saratogian, 1996 November 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 156)
  - "City man receives planning award"Saratogian, 1996 October 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 157)
  - "Planners recommend against Healy project Saratogian, 1996 September 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 158)
  - "County fully armed on the battlefield of economic development"Saratogian, 1996 June 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 159)
  - "Saratoga Springs grant from HUD is $12K short"Daily Gazette, 1996 May 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 160)
  - "City tree planting project designed to help widespread blight"Saratogian, 1997 May 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 161)
  - "Battlefield Records victory of its own", NY Times, 1997 May 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 162)
  - "Schenectady trolley bus shuttle to debut downtown in June"Daily Gazette, 1997 April 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 163)
  - "Loggers are given fines of $1000"Daily Gazette, 1996 October 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 164)
  - "Economic health of area lies in regionalization"Saratogian, 1996 April 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 165)
  - "'We could take a page from Disney', Jeff and Deane Pfeil Speaking Out"Saratogian, 1996 April 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 166)
  - "Customers who say 'wow' will return"Saratogian, Speaking Out, Deane and Jeff Pfeil, 1996 March 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 167)
  - "Chamber renews search for home"Saratogian, 1996 March 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 168)
  - "Architect as Artist", John Muse Saratogian, 1996 February 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 169)
  - Saratogian Community Guide, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 170)
  - "Speaking Out: Charlie Morrison 'Public must rationally discuss Exit 14 development,'"Saratogian, 1995 December 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 171)
  - "Chamber of Commerce to move"Saratogian, 1995 November 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 172)
  - "Chamber of Commerce to move"Saratogian, 1995 November 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 173)
  - Letter to Editor: "City Streets Dangerous Speedways"Saratogian, 1995 November 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 174)
  - "Senior housing need outweighs complaints of Wesley neighbors"Saratogian, 1995 July 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 175)
  - "Public Journalism Aims to Revitalize Public Life", Christian Science Monitor, 1995 July 24 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 176)
  - "IDA backs Saratoga flour"Saratogian, 1995 July 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 177)
  - "Saratoga in economic war with Wilton"Saratogian, 1995 June 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 178)
  - "Interlaken wants city to take over its water system"Saratogian, 1995 June 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 179)
  - "IDA appreciates support"Saratogian, 1995 May 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 180)
  - "Dalton celebrates silver anniversary"Saratogian, 1995 April 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 181)
  - "Investment plan for city on hold"Saratogian, 1995 April 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 182)
  - "County landfill to receive DEC draft permit"Saratogian, 1995 March 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 183)
  - "This is our corner grocery store"Saratogian, 1995 March 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 184)
  - "Grand Union will close", 1995 March 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 185)
  - "Pending changes in super market scene may hurt residents"Saratogian, 1995 March 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 186)
  - "Post Office may close"Albany Times Union, 1994 October 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 187)
  - "Spa City gets $15M plan"Saratogian, 1994 October 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 188)
  - "Team planning a key to success"Saratogian, 1994 September 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 189)
  - "Trucks or trees"Saratogian, 1994 September 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 190)
  - "Sewer limits questioned in Spa City"Saratogian, 1994 June 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 191)
  - "Saratoga Springs monument draws complaint", 1992 April 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 192)
  - "DEC reviewing sewer ban"Daily Gazette, 1994 June 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 193)
  - "Study shows Saratoga County the place to live", 1994 March 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 194)
  - "America's 20 hottest white-collar addresses", Wall St. Journal, 1994 March 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 195)
  - "Spa City considers decibel limit"Daily Gazette, 1993 July 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 196)
  - "Struggling to maintain its identity"Saratogian, 1992 November 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 197)
  - "City to auction 25 parcels"Saratogian, 1992 October 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 198)
  - "New Bus System begins in Spa City"Saratogian, 1992 July 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 199)
  - "Play Ball! But where?", 1992 April 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 200)
  - "Benton: Money from Land Should Go To Public Safety"Saratogian, 1992 March 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 201)
  - "NYRA, City aim to work together in off season Saratogian, 1992 February 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 202)
  - "DEC gift will help Karner Blues survive"Saratogian, 1992 February 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 203)
  - "Cemetery's neighbors concerned about safety Saratogian, 1992 January 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 204)
  - "Trust fund needed for land", Laurence Cagle, 1992 January 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 205)
  - "Enact zoning to put master plan in action", 1990 March 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 206)
  - "Revamping poorly planned growth"Saratogian, 1988 May 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 207)
  - "America's 20 Hottest White Collar Addresses", Wall St. Journal, 1994 March 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 208)
  - Historical Articles, Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1969; 1991; Undated (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 209)
  - "Urban Sprawl Sprains Western States", New York Times, Sunday, 1996 December 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 210)
  - "Group rethinks mission"Sunday Gazette, 1996 December 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 211)
  - "IDA Reviews American Tissue Plant Expansion"Saratogian, 1996 December 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 212)
  - "Pepsi, State Research Deal on Tourism", 1996 November 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 213)
  - "What's wrong with the American dream?"Saratogian, 1996 July 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 214)
  - "NYRA ought to answer to someone for track renovations"Saratogian, 1996 July 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 215)
  - "Worldwatch: Planet still in trouble despite positive signs"Saratogian, 1996 May 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 216)
  - "Spring Fundraisers aimed at providing food, open spaces"Saratogian, 1996 April 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 217)
  - "Saratoga's Winterfest gets along without snow", Sunday Gazette, 1996 February 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 218)
  - "Saratoga's annual Winterfest will go on, snow or no snow"Daily Gazette, 1996 February 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 219)
  - "S'no doubt: Winterfest's on"Saratogian, 1996 February 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 220)
  - "Winterfest '96 an off season plus for Saratoga Springs"Saratogian, 1996 February 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 221)
  - "Reprieve for Allegany State Forest", New York Times, 1996 February 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 222)
  - "Fill 'er up"Saratogian, 1996 February 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 223)
  - "Court Rules Landfill Study is Adequate"Saratogian, 1996 January 24 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 224)
  - "Winterfest Celebrates 10th Year with Expansion"Saratogian, 1996 January 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 225)
  - "Old Bryan Inn Owners Buy Canterbury"Saratogian, 1996 January 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 226)
  - "Lessons From Wesley Senior Housing Battle"Saratogian, 1996 January 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 227)
  - "Celebrating Great Community Spaces", NY Times, 1995 November 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 228)
  - "The Albany Community Land Trust", Special Section in the Albany Times Union, 1995 October 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 229)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 230)
  - "Area dance feels Pataki's Punch"Saratogian, 1995 February 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 231)
  - "Does Democracy have a future?" Poor Richards, 1995 March (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 232)
  - "State Law unites planning efforts", Robert Bristol Saratogian, 1994 August 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 233)
  - "City better off letting county handle back taxes", 1998 January 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 234)
  - "City Officials See Tough Year Ahead with Budget"Saratogian, 1995 December 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 235)
  - "Council Slashes Budget to keep Hike Below 10%"Saratogian, 1995 December 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 236)
  - "Deadline to Pass with no Budget"Saratogian, 1995 November 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 237)
  - "Lambalot: County Should Help Find Projects"Saratogian, 1995 November 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 238)
  - "Tax increase remains for city"Saratogian, 1995 November 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 239)
  - "O'Connell's about-face devious"Saratogian, 1995 November 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 240)
  - "Proposed 1996 City Budget Funds East Avenue Sewer Project"Saratogian, 1995 November 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 241)
  - "McTygue Calls for line-by-line budget review"Saratogian, 1995 November 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 242)
  - "Council Members Seek to Trim Hike"Saratogian, 1995 November 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 243)
  - "O'Connell Plans Economic Summit"Saratogian, 1995 November 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 244)
  - "Saratoga Springs Mayoral Candidates Spar in Taped Debate"Saratogian, 1995 October 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 245)
  - "Q&A": A.C. Riley on Mayoral position Saratogian, 1995 October 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 246)
  - "Curley Campaigns for Public Safety Post"Saratogian, 1995 October 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 247)
  - "New Planning Board Head hopes to keep city's vision"Saratogian, 1995 September 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 248)
  - "City Council to seek residents' input on future of properties", 1995 September 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 249)
  - "O'Hara appointed to planning board"Saratogian, 1995 September 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 250)
  - "Curley named new Public Safety Commissioner", 1995 August 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 251)
  - "Spa Council expected to pick Curley"Saratogian, 1995 August 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 252)
  - "County planning director to retire"Saratogian, 1995 August 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 253)
  - "N.C. man hired to head Tourism Bureau", 1995 July 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 254)
  - "Peck picked as candidate"Saratogian, 1995 June 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 255)
  - "A.C. Dake: 35 Years of Community Service"Saratogian, 1995 May 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 256)
  - "Preservationists honor Yaddo and Open Space board"Saratogian, 1995 May 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 257)
  - "Saratoga Board Supports Open Space"Daily Gazette, 1994 September 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 258)
  - "Letter to Editor-Democrats have own agenda"Saratogian, 1994 September 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 259)
  - "City wants to update master plan"Saratogian, 1994 September 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 260)
  - "Cub Scouts invade state park Saratogian, 1997 October 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 261)
  - "New Playground Planned at Saratoga State Park"Daily Gazette, 1997 September 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 262)
  - "Land purchased to expand state park"Sunday Gazette, 1997 April 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 263)
  - "Raceway, polo group may bid for Spa golf course"Saratogian, 1997 May 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 264)
  - "Coke is it for state parks"Saratogian, 1996 November 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 265)
  - "Foresters to set health plan for Avenue of Pines"Saratogian, 1998 February 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 266)
  - "Enjoying Outdoors State Park"Saratogian, 1997 December (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 267)
  - Open Space Research, 1994; Undated (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 268)
  - "Women won't let cancer win"Saratogian, 1996 June 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 269)
  - "Does Democracy have a future?" Poor Richards, 1995 March (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 270)
  - "Queries about school computer proposal"Saratogian, 1996 February 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 271)
  - "New Online Service Caters to Women"Saratogian, 1995 June 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 272)
  - "Merger creates largest hospice"Saratogian, 1997 March 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 273)
  - "Panel official pushes park route"Daily Gazette, 1996 March 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 274)
  - "Embattled Michael Zagata defends DEC stewardship"Daily Gazette, 1996 March 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 275)
  - "Castro opposes park bypass"Saratogian, 1996 March 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 276)
  - "Castro Rejects Truck Bypass"Daily Gazette, 1996 March 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 277)
  - "Run Truck Bypass Through State Park"Saratogian, 1996 March 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 278)
  - "Concerns about bypass task force"Saratogian, 1996 March 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 279)
  - "Residents want truck bypass"Daily Gazette, 1996 March 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 280)
  - "Attend tonight's public forum on truck bypass routes"Saratogian, 1996 March 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 281)
  - "Forum to detail proposals costs for truck bypass routes"Saratogian, 1996 March 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 282)
  - "Solving the city's truck problems", Mayor O'Connell's Letter to Editor Saratogian, 1996 March 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 283)
  - "Forum to detail proposals costs for truck bypass Saratogian, 1996 March 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 284)
  - "Truck route panel lacking environmental data: official"Daily Gazette, 1996 March 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 285)
  - "Study: Park truck route poor option"Saratogian, 1996 March 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 286)
  - "Study Pans Park Truck Routes"Daily Gazette, 1996 February 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 287)
  - "Former parks head opposes bypass"Saratogian, 1996 February 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 288)
  - "State revives plans for new Saratoga golf course"Capital District Business Review, 1996 February 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 289)
  - "Spa truck bypass plans generate debate"Albany Times Union, Undated (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 290)
  - "O'Hara buys land near course site"Saratogian, 1996 February 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 291)
  - The Source-Article on Natalie Merchant, 1996 February 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 292)
  - "Region will score with new course for state park"Saratogian, 1996 February 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 293)
  - "Engineers to review Saratoga Traffic Plans"Saratogian, 1996 February 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 294)
  - "IDA offers $9,800 for truck study"Saratogian, 1996 February 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 295)
  - "Officials set 18 hole course for park"Saratogian, 1996 February 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 296)
  - "Spa Park Truck Route Plan Faces opposition", Gazette, 1996 February 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 297)
  - "Conservation groups object to Bypass"Saratogian, 1996 February 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 298)
  - "Search for long range bypass solutions"Saratogian, 1996 February 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 299)
  - "Audubon society opposes bypass"Saratogian, 1996 February 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 300)
  - "Open Space Project, Stillwater got grants"Saratogian, 1996 January 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 301)
  - "Proposal would raise fees for state parks"Saratogian, 1996 January 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 302)
  - Letter to Editor: Richard White-Smith "Bypass Would Shatter Peace"Saratogian, 1996 January 23 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 303)
  - "Don't give up on Health Spa for Saratoga"The Saratogian, 1996 January 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 304)
  - "Group mulls Alternative Truck Routes. Truck Drivers Favor Bypass Through Park"The Saratogian, 1996 January 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 305)
  - "Manager Brings Expertise to Park"Saratogian, 1996 January 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 306)
  - "State: No Spa on Parkland"Saratogian, 1996 January 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 307)
  - "State Chips Away at Spa Golf Paperwork"Albany Times Union, 1996 January 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 308)
  - "Railroad Right of Way Might Provide Bypass Alternative"Saratogian, 1996 January 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 309)
  - "Keep bypass out of park", Letter to editor: Dennis Hodges Saratogian, 1996 January 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 310)
  - "Mayor forms bypass task force"Saratogian, 1996 January 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 311)
  - "Don't build park bypass"Saratogian, 1996 January 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 312)
  - "All roads lead to Saratoga, Something of a mixed blessing Saratogian, 1995 December 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 313)
  - "State Parks not yet sold on bypass"Saratogian, 1995 December 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 314)
  - "Truck Bypass Topic of Meeting"Saratogian, 1995 December 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 315)
  - Speaking Out: Lewis Benton III, "Park Bypass offers traffic, life quality solutions for city"Saratogian, 1995 December 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 316)
  - "Studying Bypass through Park is a wise step"Saratogian, 1995 December 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 317)
  - "County IDA to find truck bypass study"Saratogian, 1995 December 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 318)
  - "Quick action sought on truck bypass"Saratogian, 1995 December 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 319)
  - Speaking Out: B.G. "Bypass Must be in Parks Best Interest"Saratogian, 1995 December 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 320)
  - "Saratoga to Study Truck Bypass"Daily Gazette, 1995 December 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 321)
  - "Council Backs Spa Park Truck Route"Daily Gazette, 1995 December 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 322)
  - "Pataki Plan would add 1.5 billion for highways, bridges"Saratogian, 1995 December 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 323)
  - "Klein: Bypass Would Make City Safer"Saratogian, 1995 December 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 324)
  - "Bypass Through Park Would Help Traffic Problem"Saratogian, 1995 December 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 325)
  - "Park bypass proposal would disrupt wetlands"Saratogian, 1995 December 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 326)
  - "Lets get serious about sorely needed truck bypass route"Saratogian, 1995 December 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 327)
  - Letter to Editor: "Daniel's Road unsuitable for Truck Route"Saratogian, 1995 December 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 328)
  - "Bruno seeks public support for truck bypass"Saratogian, 1995 December 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 329)
  - Speaking Out: Bill Dake "Now's the time to build bypass is state park"Saratogian, 1995 December 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 330)
  - "No bypass for Saratoga", Editorial Daily Gazette, 1995 November 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 331)
  - "Park looks to protect pines"Saratogian, 1995 November 23 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 332)
  - "Truck traffic deemed priority"Saratogian, 1995 November 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 333)
  - "County looks to reroute trucks"Saratogian, 1995 November 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 334)
  - "Park System needs a plan"Portland Oregonian, 1995 September 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 335)
  - "Saratoga Battlefield on hit list", 1995 June 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 336)
  - "Health Spa/Golf Course proposed", 1995 August 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 337)
  - "Golf Course, Spa good use for land on S. Broadway", 1995 August 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 338)
  - "Lease, don't sell, State land, D'Andrea", 1995 June 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 339)
  - "State Official: Keep hands off Spa State Park", 1995 June 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 340)
  - "Save our green spaces"Saratogian, 1995 June 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 341)
  - "Keep Spa Park Public"Saratogian, 1995 June 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 342)
  - "State Park too valuable a public resource to be sold", B.G., Speaking Out Saratogian, 1995 June 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 343)
  - "Group: Keep Spa Park Land for the People", 1995 June 3 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 1)
  - "Bruno's Yard Sale" Cartoon, 1995 May 22 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 2)
  - "Keep Our Parks Available for Everyone's Uses", 1995 May 19 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 3)
  - "Critics: Sale would be Loss for Public", 1995 May 15 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 4)
  - "Agency's Caution Well-Placed in Hunt for Developers"Saratogian, 1995 May 13 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 5)
  - County IDA Wants to Sell State Property, 1995 May 10 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 6)
  - "Stokes named to Park Position", 1995 May 16 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 7)
  - "Bypass this Study"Daily Gazette, Editorial, 1996 November 5 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 8)
  - "Who'll get the 500K", Gazette, 1996 November 2 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 9)
  - "Study Something Else"Sunday Gazette, 1997 February 23 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 10)
  - "State to Control Bypass Study"Daily Gazette, 1997 February 21 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 11)
  - "Bypass Options Concern Coalition"Saratogian, 1997 February 20 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 12)
  - "Spa City Readies New Task Force on Truck Bypass Albany Times Union, 1997 February 20 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 13)
  - "Truck Committee Shifts Gears"Daily Gazette, 1997 February 19 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 14)
  - "Don't Dismiss Saratoga's Truck Problems", Sunday Gazette, 1996 November 17 (Box 4 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 15)